DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
I'll be right back.
I'll bring your brother out. Hmm?
EPISODE 2
The press release about the surgery
is scheduled to come out today.
And sir,
we were also able to expand
the pediatric cancer ward
thanks to his contribution.
However, our hospital
is the only one that is unprofitable.
But he's sick.
And in more ways than one.
So even though the net profit
of the foundation's hospital
is in the tens of billions,
we still have to cater to VIP donors?
The staff room expansion
has been put on hold,
and there's still no answer
from the foundation.
Please compile a list
of all hospital donations.
Dr. Do, why are we performing surgery,
without trying preemptive
chemotherapy first?
Well sir, i-it was the patient's demand.
There's no changing his mind.
He says that right now
he needs to keep his wits about him.
And from what's going on outside,
I can see why.
WAGE WITHHOLDING, MISMANAGEMENT,
AND ABUSE OF POWER
He's arrived at the hospital.
Dr. Ma Seong-gyu is downstairs.
Dr. Do.
Do you think you're up to it?
MONTHLY RENTALS AVAILABLE
1.5 MILLION PER MONTH (NEGOTIABLE)
"A hundred fifty per month."
Way too expensive.
GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
Park Gwang-cheol must resign!
Resign! Resign!
Pay your workers what you owe!
Pay us! Pay us!
Park Gwang-cheol must step down!
Step down! Step down!
Pay your workers what you owe!
Pay us! Pay us!
Are you a person who's sick,
or are you visiting someone?
- That's okay.
- Oh, it's all right. It's my gift to you.
So eat up, okay?
I could take it off your hands
if she doesn't want that.
Thank you.
Hey, here he comes!
Hey! Pay us, greedy pigs!
Hey! I see you! Pay us!
What makes you so much better than us?
Hey! We're patients too.
Look, he's going inside.
- You need to stay out here.
- Why does he get to go in ahead of us?
We're patients!
Let me ask you something.
A-All right.
Is it true that I'm actually sick?
The cancer diagnosis was legitimate?
Yes, I'm afraid so, sir.
Nobody believes it's true.
I lied about being sick to avoid
the National Assembly audit.
I pretended to collapse
in order to delay my trial,
and now that I really am sick
these folks decided to come down here
just to raise hell outside.
Well, stress can exacerbate your symptoms.
Dr. Do is a fantastic surgeon,
and he's extremely knowledgeable.
Rest assured, you're in great hands.
You've got a bright future here.
Thank you, sir. My name is Ma Seong-gyu.
Before we go to my room,
let's go see
that pediatric cancer ward I financed.
I couldn't show my face back then
because of the trial.
I heard you put my name up on a plaque.
Yes, we certainly did.
This is the story of a lone wolf.
Hey, Gye Su-jeong.
I need to borrow this.
A solitary figure who emerged
in the era of the mafia in white,
an age in which the practice of medicine,
where life and death hang in the balance…
- This is an emergency!
- …is driven by money and power.
- She belongs to no group.
- She took my chair!
- She is unaffiliated with any department.
- Gye Su-jeong!
- This woman, right here…
- Come back here! Gye Su-jeong!
- She despises authority
- and answers to no one.
- Hey, wait!
Her only weapons are her medical license
and the surgical skills
she honed from the ground up.
No pneumothorax. Can you hear me?
Can you tell me your name?
Lee Ju-hui.
Juvenile diabetes.
- Check her EMR stat.
- Okay. I'm on it.
Well, this is embarrassing.
Who was that crazy girl?
Gye Su-jeong, general surgeon.
Also known as…
Doctor X.
Chairman Park Gwang-cheol…
Seriously, this is just…
…to avoid serving of his sentence.
Are we seriously working with her?
We have to.
It was Director Bu's decision
and we are short on doctors.
But she does whatever she wants.
It's completely ridiculous.
- Yeah, but it was an emergency.
- I know, but…
now everyone I know
is gonna see me on the news.
Don't worry, you look amazing on camera.
Oh, don't say that.
You did good.
You want revenge?
Let's go distract her,
that way she can't focus.
Okay. Okay.
Well…
Hey.
- Uh, want some coffee?
- Yeah, coffee.
Yeah, mmm, coffee.
Excuse me, excuse me. Earbuds.
Oh, man.
Oh, yeah.
You should assist Dr. Do
with his surgery, okay?
I thought you were gonna do it.
No, I can't be the one to assist.
He'd know right away that I was only there
because I don't trust his surgical skills.
Someone at your level should assist,
so he doesn't get suspicious.
Okay. But, um, how did Dr. Do end up--
It was decided over drinks.
It seems Dr. Do kept filling
Chairman Park's glass that day,
and he was in such a good mood
that he appointed him primary surgeon.
Who picks their surgeon on a whim though?
Well, because everybody wanted to do it,
and he decided to choose
the one who'd walk on eggshells
and grovel at his feet the most
out of all the hospital's surgeons.
And Dr. Do simply couldn't refuse.
- Oh, wow.
- That's garbage.
Is it?
Don't make eye contact with her.
Don't make eye contact.
Yeah, okay.
- I'm not looking at her. I'm not looking.
- Neither am I.
We'll lose if we do.
The staff room used to be
my home away from home
and now I feel so uncomfortable here.
That privacy screen over there
could be helpful in this situation.
- Yeah, good idea.
- Let's set it up.
Okay, let's do it.
Now I'm anxious because I can't see her.
I can't tell what she's up to.
- Put it away?
- I think we'd better.
- Let's put it away. Sorry.
- I'm a little scared.
Lift.
There we go. There we go.
I'm uncomfortable again
now that I can see her.
I'm uncomfortable when I can see her,
and anxious when I can't.
She's so annoying.
Oh, Dr. Do. Hello.
Those go over there.
W-What?
Oh, yes, sir.
Dr. Gye, nice to see you again.
Hey, who told you to put them there?
This is a walkway here.
They don't go there.
- What?
- You need to put them on the desk.
Oh, uh, yeah.
But this is Dr. Gye Su-jeong's desk…
Let's do this, intern.
There we go.
- What's this?
- My terms of employment.
"Accompanying director rounds, attending
rounds, and attending company dinners."
That is not something I do.
"Ghostwriting papers and compiling
research materials for attendings."
That is not something I do.
I know, I heard.
I didn't bring these in here
so you could draft me a paper.
I just picked out some materials
that might help.
You can read them at your leisure.
Only…
there's just no room for them
anywhere else.
Our staff room is so very small.
Uh, well, we could split them up
and put some on my desk.
- That'll free up some space for Dr. Gye.
- Hey, Park Tae-gyeong.
- Hey, Park Tae-gyeong. Park Tae-gyeong.
- Dr. Gye?
Boy, I don't know if there's
anywhere else she can go.
- Nice.
- Dr. Tae-gyeong. How's it going?
From now on, your job is
to be Dr. Gye's surveillance camera.
What?
I want you to keep an eye on her.
Uh, well, I'm an intern.
I have to do my studies.
I managed to get all my studying done
while juggling multiple attendings.
You just have to watch one mad dog.
- "Mad dog"?
- Yeah.
Yeah. We all call her mad dog.
Because she's crazy as a rabid dog.
So now it's her nickname.
But isn't that a little childish?
Mocking someone just because
you don't understand them?
I mean, it's exactly
what bullies do on a playground.
- Hey, I'm not some kind of bully.
- Okay, the surveillance camera is now on.
Here we go.
Dr. Gye, I've been looking for you.
Are you working here?
Why don't we go in then?
Oh, you left your bag behind, huh?
Well, I've got my wallet. I'll get this…
One strawberry cake,
one Earl Grey pound cake, one croffle set,
and a large vanilla latte, extra sweet.
Go get her.
Bring that mad dog here right now.
She may have overreacted a little, uh,
in the heat of the moment.
Hey. Mr. New-Director, listen up.
If I die, there will be a lot of people
whose lives will…
Oh, sir. I'm sure they'll be
so sad and devastated.
…be easier.
They'll all be glad.
They'll say everything was my fault.
They'll dump all the shit
they created right into my tomb.
Dying…
is not an option.
You have to save my life, no matter what.
Got it?
Well, answer me!
- Yes, sir.
Ah, I'm glad you have a healthy appetite.
Oh, Dr. Gye, maybe I should get your bag.
You had your wallet? Then why didn't you…
- I'm broke.
- You have no money?
"Terms of employment.
Absolutely no personal conversations"?
What if I order an extra slice
of blueberry cake--
I spent my allowance.
All right, so you're getting an allowance.
Who from?
- Ms. Jang.
- I see.
So she manages your money for you.
Do you live with her?
I mean, you're a doctor.
You can't be getting a kid's allowance.
How much money do you get?
A hundred thousand won…
Well, that would be plenty
of money per day to--
- …per month.
- What?
You can't be expected to live on that.
Is she blackmailing you?
I'm in debt.
What? Uh, deep in debt?
Mmm. I get in trouble if I waste it.
Oh.
W-What do you mean you get in trouble?
Does she, like, hit you?
Mmm. She sure does.
She hit me yesterday
for using up my allowance.
Did Ms. Jang by any chance
take your passport
or identification card?
Mmm. Ms. Jang manages everything.
Su-jeong likes to eat her cake.
Su-jeong, you want a little cake?
Cake!
If you want cake, go to work
and earn some money, doctor-slave.
Put your hands up!
I want you to sign this.
I took out a loan under your name.
- I wanna eat more of this.
- Yeah, yeah. Please, have another.
Uh, feel free to order
as many as you want.
I'm buying. Go ahead and eat up.
You're a good person.
I wanna finish all this.
Have you been craving
anything in particular?
- Jjajangmyeon.
- Hmm.
- Next time I'll take you out to dinner.
- Let's do it today.
When do you get off work?
I'm done at 6:00.
Oh, I don't get off that early.
Just clock out at 6:00.
- Please insert your card.
- Ah, those probably aren't easy to use
for the patients or the elderly,
even with someone to assist.
- Excuse me.
- I tried it earlier.
I'm young, and even I had trouble with it.
It's hard to read, and you get nervous…
And you're aware
of all the people behind you.
- Right. That made me freeze up even more.
- Excuse me, sorry.
I felt like such a loser.
I was like, "Can I even do this?"
Can I help you with that?
Oh, yes, please.
Oh, thanks for your help.
- At least it benefits the patients, right?
- Please insert your card.
It benefits the hospital.
Does it look like
it benefits the patients?
Oh, I didn't think that
you considered people like that.
Uh, don't let it get to you,
what happened in the staff room earlier.
What?
You know, getting kicked out
by the others.
Rejected.
Oh… I had no idea.
Maybe you just need to lay low
for a little while, you know?
Unnie!
- Hey, I could've done that.
- Oh. There you are.
I'm just trying
to use the kiosk right now.
Oh, how's Ju-hui doing?
- Well, the pain is gone, so…
- Good.
- She's mad though.
- Wait, what is she mad about?
Wouldn't you be?
She's only a kid,
and for her whole life she's been sick.
- And now it's cancer.
- Please insert your card.
- May I have your card?
- Oh.
They need an interim payment.
What, do they think we'll skip town
without paying?
Hold on, wait. Wait.
Hey. What's that? What's with that vest?
Go, get that thing outta here.
Go on, do it.
Yes sir.
- Isn't that amazing?
- You can't be in here.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
What's going on?
Why are you people doing this?
- I said, let go!
- That's right.
- Oh, are you scared?
- Yeong-ju.
Is that why you're doing this?
What the hell are you doing?
- Hey, that's mine!
- We didn't come to the hospital
to protest.
My daughter's a patient here, sir.
- What are you doing?
- Yeong-ju!
- Don't push her wheelchair!
It's true, my daughter is a patient.
- We're here to visit her.
- Let go first, then we can talk.
- I'm here for my family.
- Hey, hey. That lunatic. Why, that…
Why didn't you get rid of her?
- You said you'd take care of it!
- I came here to be with my niece
- and sister!
- Hey, come on…
- Yeong-ju…
- Um, excuse me!
- It says this card's been maxed out.
- Oh, the card, the card. My card.
The vest, my wallet's in that vest.
Could you give it to her?
I said let go! Are you crazy?
- Hey, hey…
- Seriously, why are you doing this?
- Let go! I said let go!
- First let go, then we can talk.
- This is ridiculous!
- We could work this all out,
- if you let go of her!
- What is your problem?
People with nothing
are always the loudest.
They're all such pathetic losers.
- Uh, Chairman--
- Pathetic losers? Pathetic losers?
- And whose fault do you think all this is?
- Hey.
Give my aunt her pay!
- I said give it to her!
- Ju-hui!
- Give my aunt her pay!
Ju-hui, stop it!
Oh, gosh. Ju-hui! Ju-hui!
Ju-hui!
- Ju-hui, hold on, I'm coming!
- Get this girl off of me!
- What do you think you're doing?
- Ju-hui! Calm down!
- Come on, let her go!
- Hey, let go of my daughter!
- I'll get you out of here, Chairman.
- You're going to get hurt. No
Let go. You'll get hurt.
Hey, hold on now, stop that! Ju-hui!
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, my gosh.
- She's bleeding. Help her!
- Let me see.
Let go of me. I said let go of me.
Ju-hui.
- Ju-hui.
- Unbelievable.
Are you okay?
- Ju-hui, are you okay?
- Where'd he go?
- Ju-hui. Hey!
- Hey, where did Chairman Park go?
- Ju-hui. Ju-hui.
- Hey, you're bleeding.
It's true…
We really are pathetic losers.
Hey.
Lee Ju-hui.
Lee Ju-hui!
Ju-hui. Ju-hui.
- Ju-hui.
- What's that?
Is that blood on the floor?
You had me worried.
You're back already?
Where's Chairman Park?
I parked him.
Hey!
Mmm. She'll be here soon, your sister.
She's in a brief meeting
- with the hospital staff.
- Okay.
- When she comes, you can go.
- Huh? Why?
I'm your mother, I'm staying right here.
Two balls and one strike.
Here's the fourth pitch.
And it's right down the middle, strike!
The count is 2-2. Man.
Would you mind
stepping outside with me for a second?
I'd like to discuss
your daughter's surgery with you.
Okay.
Can you wait until my aunt gets here?
Oh, let me get you something, Doctor.
- Here you go.
- Oh. Thanks very much.
Dr. Gye.
Juvenile diabetes and pancreatoblastoma.
It's a very rare case.
Really? What's the prognosis?
- It's hopeless.
- A lost cause?
How could he miss that?
The game's hopeless.
You're really one of a kind, you know?
Excuse me.
Back-to-back hits…
- Hmm.
- Where are you going?
Dr. Gye!
W-What about Dr. Gye? What happened?
- She disappeared.
- Disappeared?
Where to?
Yes, Doctor. Uh, Dr. Gye should be…
Sorry? What incident?
No, when did…
She disappeared a minute ago.
- Uh, Dr. Gye. So, uh…
- Where's Dr. Gye? Show your face.
- Hmm? I know you're here.
- Isn't that her?
Yeah, there she is.
Oh, this is her. Right?
- That's her.
- She can really put it away.
Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
- Dr. Gye!
- What are you doing?
What's going on?
Uh, Dr. Gye.
What were you doing before
we met at the coffee shop earlier?
- I was in the hallway.
- What were you doing in the hallway?
I saw a patient
lying there with dizziness,
so I asked her a few questions
and sent her to the ENT.
She had Ménière's.
You're telling me that a temp like you
diagnosed Ménière's disease, huh?
Would you keep it down, please?
Is that really what you're all
up in arms about?
That patient was waiting
to be seen by Internal Medicine
and now she's over in ENT,
lying on a couch.
- What about the tests?
- We did them.
She's unable to hear low frequencies
and she's got nystagmus.
- It's Ménière's.
- No issue then.
No, that's not the only issue here.
She crossed the line and interfered
in another department's patient care.
She'd spent years going from one local
clinic to another in the countryside,
getting put on IVs and medication
as she grew weaker.
Her kid finally brought her in
to a major hospital.
No need to put her through the wringer.
Even her own kid chalked it up
to geriatric depression
and disregarded her symptoms.
Indeed. That's why she grabbed me
and cried on my shoulder.
It was the first time
she'd been correctly diagnosed,
and she was so grateful.
And I was so embarrassed.
By the way, did she just give us an order?
- Mmm.
- Yes.
So the rumors are true,
you really are disrespectful.
Fascinating.
Since when does a scalpel jockey
know how to diagnose patients?
Are you saying us scalpel jockeys
can't come up with a diagnosis on our own?
- You're completely out of line.
- Well, now…
Well, suppose I told one of your patients
not to have surgery. How would you feel?
Let's calm down. It's not a fight between
Internal Medicine and General Surgery.
The problem is that Dr. Gye over here
overstepped her boundaries.
I think we should just focus on…
- Hey, uh, just apologize to them already.
- …making sure that…
Oh, no need to apologize to me.
I just came to put a face to the name
and observe the infamous snake Su-jeong.
Don't be a stranger, huh?
How intriguing.
I'm leaving.
Oh, a-an apology isn't enough for me.
She needs to face disciplinary action
or a pay cut.
Neither would apply to me, actually.
I'm just a temp.
How dare you keep talking back to me!
Well, she's talking back, all right.
But she did make a good point, didn't she?
Okay, so for now, why don't you just go?
Let us deal with this internally
and we'll tell you what we decide. Okay?
Deal with it properly.
I'm not gonna just forget about it.
Yeah, okay.
Goodbye, Dr.
That guy's so loud.
He's known for his temper, now I see why.
He must pop antacids like candy.
What do you think you're doing
diagnosing patients who aren't yours
in the hallway?
Donkkaseu.
How many more helpings am I allowed?
It's good.
- What?
- I think you should read the room…
It's hard to find really good donkkaseu.
- Uh, I'll get you some more later. Just…
- I'm not… Wait, hey, y- you…
Hey, Park Tae-gyeong, what were you doing?
Oh, I apologize. I didn't think
she'd get in trouble so fast.
Although, I'm not sure
that what she did was terrible.
- She was just trying to help a lady who--
- You're right. She was only helping.
But she overstepped her boundaries.
- And she planned the whole thing.
- She did what?
She's trying to get back in the staff room
by making trouble
until we give her desk back to her.
Don't tell me you got rid of
that poor woman's desk.
That's such a horrible thing to do.
You're absolutely right.
I think we may have been
totally manipulated by her.
- Exactly.
- Seriously?
Do you really think she's capable of
something like that? I mean, look at her.
In order to get
another helping of donkkaseu,
she's trying to disguise herself
by going like this with her hair.
Does that look like an evil genius to you?
Come on.
Okay, our first patient is Park
Gwang-cheol, 67 years old.
He's a VIP who has generously
supported the hospital over the years.
We must make every effort to ensure
he is comfortable during his stay here.
And Dr. Do Yun-sik
will be the primary surgeon.
Oh, so that guy's a VIP?
The diagnosis is cancer in
the head of the pancreas,
measuring about 4 cm.
So we decided that the Whipple Procedure
is the best option.
- I'll do my best--
- I object.
There's a possibility the cancer
has invaded the SMA or SMV.
Even if it has, it's the same plan.
The VIP has refused chemotherapy.
Ah, first of all,
I'll try to preserve the SMA
as much as possible during the surgery.
If you leave the blood vessels,
it'll be an R2 resection.
Why even operate then?
After surgery, he'll get the chemotherapy.
You should resect it along
with the blood vessel, R0.
- Unbelievable.
- R0?
She is driving me crazy.
R0? Do you think we don't do that
because we don't want to?
You trying to sabotage us?
It's basic surgical knowledge
you don't mess with the SMA.
Or don't you know that?
Geez.
I'd be okay with messing with it,
but I guess you wouldn't be.
Are you saying you can do it, Dr. Gye?
- Yes.
- So you'd do it yourself?
- Mmm.
- If you fail, this hospital--
Except…
it's not in my nature to fail.
Okay, the next patient is Lee Ju-hui,
a 15-year-old female.
Dr. Do Yun-sik is her attending.
The VIP requested
that his surgery be moved up,
so Lee Ju-hui has agreed
to have her surgery postponed--
Lee Ju-hui's surgery…
will be performed by Dr. Gye.
Director.
This patient is crucial to my case report.
- I wanna keep her.
- And I really don't want her.
You think it's acceptable
to postpone a surgery?
Explain her case.
Ah, right.
She has an 8 cm tumor
in the pancreatic body and tail.
Uh, based on the imaging,
further evaluation for pancreatoblastoma
was recommended,
so we performed
an ultrasound-guided biopsy,
which confirmed the diagnosis.
There was no evidence
of distant metastasis.
She's back.
Don't cause trouble, or you'll get fired.
Keep a low profile.
It's not like they won't let you operate.
You really think
she can keep a low profile?
You know how she is.
- Whoa! I almost dropped it.
- Whoa.
You know, if Dr. Do performs the surgery,
he could kill someone.
That's how it's done.
Is he really that bad?
He got where he is through papers,
research and cronyism.
Not because he has skills.
The hospital doctor's world is built on…
their rep,
prestige,
and authority.
And a lot of other factors
that support that world.
Take those away,
and they wouldn't be doctors.
If they wouldn't be doctors without them,
then they weren't doctors
- in the first place.
- Hey. And when those things…
…collapse,
that's our opportunity.
Oh, for Jenga's sake.
Bend over. Here we go.
Loser's punishment.
She must be fueled by blind ambition.
I mean, Lee Ju-hui's a patient too.
Maybe she gets paid more
for surgery on a VIP.
Watch her tomorrow too.
And tell her to go apologize.
I'm off.
- Okay. Have a good night.
- See ya.
Just in case she comes back here tomorrow…
Complications include pancreatic fistula,
peritonitis, infections,
blood clots, lung and heart complications,
bowel obstruction,
and the possibility
of postoperative bleeding.
So, do you have any questions for us?
Oh, uh, could I just ask,
what happened to the other doctor?
I thought he was a big shot around here,
so…
Oh, she's really skilled too.
You can take it from me.
- Ah.
- Seriously?
He said I was an extremely rare case
or whatever
and that he wanted
to do the surgery himself.
What a joke.
How long will she be in surgery?
Uh, we think it will take around
three to four hours to complete.
Oh.
- That's so long.
- Mm-hmm.
I don't want the operation.
- Sorry?
- What are you talking about?
What, are you nuts?
Hey.
You can't back out now.
We already cashed in your college fund.
Your focus needs to be
on the surgery right now.
Even if I live, no college
is ever gonna want to accept me.
That's why I always tell you
to study or work.
I looked it up too.
It said that my chances
are really not very good.
For someone like me, it's usually this,
isn't it?
Geez.
That damned Internet.
It totally messes kids up.
Uh, don't pay attention to her. We're fine
with that doctor doing the surgery. Okay?
Miss, you need to get the surgery--
Ju-hui.
- How dare you say you won't even try?
- Stop it, both of you. Okay?
Give me the consent form.
We'll just sign it now
and go outside to fight among ourselves.
No, miss, please give that back.
- Ju-hui!
- I'm sick of this.
- Hey!
- Just let me talk!
I'm sick of all this, that's why.
I'm tired, Mom.
I'm only 15 years old.
Do you know what
the other kids are saying?
They call me a junkie
because I give myself
injections in the bathoom every day.
If you didn't get your insulin shots,
you'd die. They don't know anything.
But now I have a deadly illness
on top of that.
And, Mom, you've got your health problems.
It's gotta be really hard
to take care of me as well.
I'm your mom. It's not hard.
Then what about you, Auntie?
You've probably
got it the worst of all of us.
You've got a dying niece
and a disabled sister to care for.
You have to work twice as hard
as everyone else because of us,
then come home and do work at the house.
You deserve better than that.
I can handle it.
I can't handle you giving up though.
Give me that.
Stop it!
Just leave me alone.
Just… just go, all of you.
Just let me die!
We all die sometime, don't we?
So, there's no rush.
You could die today or next week.
It makes no difference in the long run.
- Dr. Gye, maybe don't mention--
- It's all the same.
But if I don't operate,
you'll be dead within a month.
And if you get the surgery,
you'll still die.
But it won't be for…
a hundred years or so.
She's 15, that's about right, isn't it?
Uh, well…
And only if I do your surgery.
Because I never fail.
I'll save you. No matter what it takes.
Your choice.
Do you wanna die in a month,
or live for a hundred years?
"Do you wanna die in a month,
or live for a hundred years?"
Wow. That whole time
I kept explaining things to them.
And your line worked like magic.
If you fail, though,
we'll be in serious trouble.
Of course we will. Someone could die.
But you…
I mean, come on. You've been studying
her chart nonstop since…
Wait, what's this?
You've been reading Chairman Park's chart
this whole time?
Dr. Gye.
When you do Lee Ju-hui's surgery,
please do your best.
I mean, I could do it, but…
…as you know, Director Bu
has me doing Chairman Park's surgery.
We got the consent form signed today.
You might wanna consider
switching surgeries with me.
Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
And why is it that you keep saying that?
You don't have the skills to do it.
- Okay, that's it!
- Please don't.
If only you were as competent
as you are stubborn.
We can hear you.
We heard that loud and clear!
Doctor, people are watching.
Please calm down, Dr. Ma.
Oh, so that's how it us, huh?
Oh, boy!
Hey, wait.
Su-jeong, come eat!
- She must be preparing for surgery.
- Mm-hmm.
Surgery is the only thing
she likes more than eating.
Only one each! I cooked one per person.
Hey, aren't you two ever going home?
You're both eating three meals a day here.
Oh! Are we celebrating?
- Because you made galbijjim.
- Uh, yeah.
Kimchi. Mmm.
DOCTOR DO YUN-SIK
You don't have the skills to do it.
Lee Ju-hui's surgery
will be performed by Dr. Gye.
Found it.
GUSEO UNIVERSITY SEONAM MEDICAL CENTER
Oh, Lee Ju-hui's pancreatic cancer surgery
is today as well, isn't it?
Where is it, OR 5?
It's not too late to switch.
Let's do a time-out.
Please stop what you're doing
and pay attention.
What is the patient's name
and registration number?
11384675, Park Gwang-cheol.
OPERATION TIME, TIME, ANESTHESIA TIME
Scalpel.
No issues with anesthesia,
and vitals are stable.
Then we'll begin with
the time-out. Lee Ju-hui's sub--
Wipe.
Harmonic.
Vessel loop.
Long Kelly.
I can see the SMA.
Does that surprise you?
It's like you've never seen it before.
This…
It shouldn't be like this.
What's wrong, Doctor?
It's spread too much.
It's much worse than I expected.
The tumor…
- It's completely…
- It's encasing the vessel.
The SMA invasion is pervasive.
Yun-sik…
What are you going to do?
Even if we do a partial resection,
the prognosis won't change.
We'll have to…
close him back up.
Listen to me.
This isn't just any patient.
The fate of the hospital depends on…
The mic.
Dr. Do.
Is your plan really
just to give up trying?
Excuse me?
What if I tell you that's not an option?
But Director, what else can I do?
Any further resection could do the patient
more harm than good.
You're going to tell him you cut into him
just to close him back up again?
But…
Wouldn't it be better if you could say
you did everything you possibly could
until the very end?
Then if we could contact
the patient's family…
There is no one.
There's no one here. Why would they be?
Damn it…
They're all just waiting for him to die.
His family keeps calling,
one right after the other,
to check on his chances of survival.
Bu Seung-gwon calling.
You know we're not religious.
I'm trying everything I can.
Should we start
believing in something now?
I will if Ju-hui gets better.
If she doesn't, I won't.
It'll be their loss.
Why don't you get something to eat?
No, I'm okay.
Ju-hui didn't eat before her surgery,
and neither should I.
There's a chocolate bar in there.
Help yourself.
Unnie.
Look what I found.
TO MY FAMILY
Transecting the pancreas.
Stapler, 60, black.
Thank goodness.
The adhesion isn't severe.
It is still pretty big though.
I'll get it, Dr. Gye.
Focus on the surgery.
- Hello. This is OR 5.
- Right angle.
Uh, this is Park Tae-gyeong, the intern.
Go ahead.
Not bad.
Tell Dr. Gye…
she's needed in OR 1 right away.
Sorry?
Uh, Dr. Gye is in the middle of surgery
at the moment.
Tell her it's an emergency.
Uh, I'm sorry, Director. I can't do that.
We need more time here.
Dr. Gye has to stay
and finish this surgery.
This is Gye Su-jeong. I'll be right there.
Dr. Gye?
Are you giving up on Ju-hui's surgery?
- Out of the way.
- Why would you do that?
Because she's not a VIP?
Because she's from a poor family
with a disabled mother?
Priority.
So, by priority,
do you mean getting ahead?
Is that the kind of doctor you are?
I said get out of the way.
Whenever the other doctors
would bad-mouth you
for chasing money and success,
I never believed it. But now…
How could you do this?
You're a doctor!
You should look after your patient
until the end!
You promised her a hundred years!
You said you'd save her
no matter what it takes.
That's more like it.
You're a doctor!
You should look after your patient
until the end!
You promised her a hundred years!
You said you'd save her
no matter what it takes.
- Uh, what? How…
- I called Doctor Gye in.
- Director!
- I'm taking over.
Director, you can't do this!
Wait a sec. I don't…
- What about the surgery in OR 5 then?
- Go see if you're worried.
Oh, you're such a b--
Are you out of your mind?
Did you just abandon your patient?
Dr. Bae Heung-gon is already there.
Hey, move, move it! And let me through.
Move! Out of my way!
Dr. Gye.
He's all yours, I'm counting on you.
- Just as I thought. Move aside, please.
- What are you going to do?
RESECTION PHASE
(RESECTION AND VASCULAR DISSECTION)
I'm going to do a saphenous harvest.
- What?
- Open the drape and disinfect the leg.
Scissors, please.
W-why the leg?
What do you think you're doing?
Why are you changing procedure
all of a sudden? Hey, the next surgery--
Get Dr. Jo Won-jin from OR 5, please.
What? Hey!
I'm on it. Dr. Kim, please go to OR 5.
That shouldn't be necessary.
Hold mean BP at 70.
- Yes, Doctor.
- Dr. Jo, seriously? You too?
How can you abandon your patient?
If only you were this concerned
about professional ethics all the time.
- What's the EBL?
- 100 cc.
Prepare for vascular anastomosis.
Get the 7-0 Prolene and the loupes ready.
Don't tell me you're going to…
cut the vessel.
I guess writing all those papers
actually gave you a decent eye.
You there.
I'd like you to assist me.
You wanna cut the vessel?
How do I assist
when I don't know what you're doing?
We're doing an en bloc resection
of the pancreatic head, including the SMA.
What?
Huh? Uh, wait…
So you're saying…
that she did all of this in an hour?
Yes, Doctor.
Did the surgery go well?
In just an hour?
There isn't even any blood.
What kind of doctor talks that?
Sorry?
Hemostasis.
Uh, right. Right. Uh, the hemostasis
was complete according to Dr. Jo Won-jin.
So this…
This is Gye Su-jeong's work?
After harvesting the saphenous vein
from the thigh,
we'll proceed with the en bloc resection
of the pancreatic cancer,
including the SMA and SMV.
We will reconstruct the SMA
with the saphenous vein,
and use an 8 mm synthetic graft
for the SMV.
W-wait!
What did you just say?
Doctor, is she-- Is she really gonna…
Have you lost your mind?
Are you practicing on a patient?
- Are you really gonna do this?
- Yes, I am.
There's no telling what might happen!
It's too risky!
If you fail, he'll die.
He'll die from bowel necrosis!
Dr. Do Yun-sik.
Do it Dr. Gye Su-jeong's way.
And, by the way, Doctor Gye Su-jeong
was not in this operating room today.
Self-retaining retractor
and loupes, please.
Harmonic.
Estimated blood loss is 320 ccs.
The bowel anastomosis is complete.
Please monitor the drain output closely
for any signs of bleeding.
You can do that yourself, Dr. Gye…
Oh, don't tell me you're clocking out now…
You should at least do this much.
If you want to call yourself a doctor.
Director.
Since she did two surgeries today,
we'll have to charge double.
And neither the patient's family,
nor the public,
will hear about this from us.
- I understand.
- In return, we'd like payment in cash.
I'll be back soon.
Sir, I'm sorry.
Yun-sik.
Closing him back up
was your first instinct.
You didn't think about
what else you could have done.
Your first instinct was to give up.
- But--
- And by that point,
you were basically gone.
I was there though.
I offered to assist
and I stayed until the end of surgery.
Just so I could do something.
Can you imagine how humiliated I felt?
Facing that insurmountable wall,
knowing that I don't have the skills to…
to get over the top.
I…
But I still…
I still stayed in the OR the whole time.
I persevered.
And I'll continue to persevere.
And…
I know I'm gonna make a name for myself
here one day. I want to.
And fulfill every one of my dreams.
Director.
You know…
…what my dream is.
I do.
I understand.
That guy can be really sappy.
He's not a very good surgeon either.
But it was pretty cool of him to say.
Mm-hmm.
Uh, what are you two doing there?
Uh, h-have you seen Dr. Gye?
Ugh. I'm so sick of hearing that name.
Gye Su-jeong.
You're going a little overboard
with the surveillance thing.
Yeah, what would she be doing here,
in the men's locker room?
Oh, right.
- What?
- Well, it's just that earlier…
It's nothing.
Huh.
Uh, she really did two surgeries
in an hour?
Yeah.
And what I think?
She planned it. She knew that she was
gonna have to do both surgeries.
- It's the only explanation.
- For real?
Oh, shit.
I had no idea.
Gosh. I'll be on my way then.
What's with that guy?
TO MY FAMILY
MY AUNT, ME, MY MOM
To my family.
Mom, Auntie…
Forget a hundred years.
I might end up dying today.
Mom, Auntie, you two only love me
because I'm your daughter and niece.
If I weren't, you wouldn't have
liked me that much.
But I think I would have liked you both,
even if you weren't my mom or my aunt.
You two are really amazing
and wonderful people.
That's what I really wanted to say,
instead of something like, "I love you."
- Yeah, that's right. He's out of surgery.
- It was you, wasn't it?
No, it wasn't me.
I was on your side, if you recall.
That's not true at all.
What are you talking about?
I said we should do it all together.
- Oh, come on.
- You don't remember?
You've been blocking me
every step of the way.
Don't you think I know that?
I can't imagine why you would
feel that way. It makes no sense.
Next time we meet, let's be friends.
Instead of always
looking after each other,
let's just have fun together.
Let's make sure we meet again.
- I brought beer.
- Nice!
- Does she know we're having bulgogi?
- Yeah.
Oh, she must be there by now.
My goodness.
The two of you certainly are very excited.
Ooh! You bet, you bet
You bet, you bet!
I'm so excited
Got cash coming down like rain
Filling up my wallet
Making me happy
LUCKY BATHHOUSE
BANANA MILK
You know,
Chairman Park gave this to the hospital
so we could organize a dinner
for the surgical team.
Then all the more reason
for me to take it off your hands.
CHAIRMAN PARK IN RECOVERY
SEARCH AND SEIZURE OF SUN & STEEL
That's right. You need to be alive
to face punishment and pay the price.
Chairman, let's see
how many more years you've got.
Everyone keep looking.
I need that surgical technique in detail.
Okay.
Doctor Gye had to have known beforehand
that she'd need to use
that technique, right?
That's not important right now.
What matters more is what this all means.
So, what does it mean?
That she really is a snake,
who pushes ahead with surgery
that puts her patient's life on the line,
for her own gain.
Doctor Gye, why are you out here
instead of at your desk?
The GS lackeys got rid of my desk.
Uh, the thing is…
It's okay. I'm fine out here.
Well, Ms. Jang has received
what was due for in this case.
It was asking a lot,
and I want you to know I appreciate it.
It wasn't asking that much.
Dr. Gye Su-jeong.
Oh, I found it.
Ah, this is the surgical technique
Dr. Gye used.
There's an article about it
from seven years ago.
Hmm.
"Gastrointestinal surgeons
at Cuba's Cubanacan University Hospital
successfully performed
an en bloc resection
with an SMA reconstruction,
providing an unexpected cure
for a patient
who had previously been
considered inoperable.
However, the patient died
two months after the surgery."
You can't avoid failure forever.
It seems like
you've already failed, director.
"The patient's cause of death
is currently unknown."
"The name of the surgeon
was never revealed,
but the alias written on the chart was…
Dr. X."
DOCTOR X: MAFIA IN WHITE
So you're saying
Dr. Gye Su-jeong is Dr. X?
What are you doing?
Right now we're losing blood faster
than we're losing time.
Don't do it every day! Don't you dare!
The hospital's been in a tizzy
over the last few days
- and it's all because of her.
- Transfer her now.
No. We have to treat her here,
no matter what.
There's a doctor who can
handle the operation.
I have temporarily assigned
another doctor here.
- And who is that?
- The surgery has begun.
Fire her immediately.
We need to make sure
she never works in medicine again!
Dr. Gye, please. Please wake up!